emasbatang.com 2012-02-22

# Emasbatang.com | An SEO Friendly PHPLD Directory - About Us

### Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we providethis notice explaining our online information practices and the choices youcan make about the way your information is collected and used. To make thisnotice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every pointwhere personally identifiable information may be requested.

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads onthis site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts tovisitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other siteson the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content networkprivacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.htmlTracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Googlesown privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to trackusers activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness andother reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies Emasbatang.com | An SEO Friendly PHPLD Directoryhas no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

Collection of Personal Information

When visiting Emasbatang.com | An SEO Friendly PHPLD Directory, the IP address usedto access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information ispurely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement andgather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, anyrecorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are notresponsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be awarethat the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Emasbatang.com | An SEO Friendly PHPLD Directorythen you may contact us at admin@emasbatang.com.
